[Login](https://us.dantelabs.com/account/login "Login
")

   United Kingdom (GBP £)

* Afghanistan (AFN ؋)
* Åland Islands (EUR €)
* Albania (ALL L)
* Algeria (DZD د.ج)
* Andorra (EUR €)
* Angola (USD $)
* Anguilla (XCD $)
* Antigua & Barbuda (XCD $)
* Argentina (USD $)
* Armenia (AMD դր.)
* Aruba (AWG ƒ)
* Ascension Island (SHP £)
* Australia (AUD $)
* Austria (EUR €)
* Azerbaijan (AZN ₼)
* Bahamas (BSD $)
* Bahrain (USD $)
* Bangladesh (BDT ৳)
* Barbados (BBD $)
* Belarus (USD $)
* Belgium (EUR €)
* Belize (BZD $)
* Benin (XOF Fr)
* Bermuda (USD $)
* Bhutan (USD $)
* Bolivia (BOB Bs.)
* Bosnia & Herzegovina (BAM КМ)
* Botswana (BWP P)
* Brazil (USD $)
* British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $)
* British Virgin Islands (USD $)
* Brunei (BND $)
* Bulgaria (BGN лв.)
* Burkina Faso (XOF Fr)
* Burundi (BIF Fr)
* Cambodia (KHR ៛)
* Cameroon (XAF Fr)
* Canada (CAD $)
* Cape Verde (CVE $)
* Caribbean Netherlands (USD $)
* Cayman Islands (KYD $)
* Central African Republic (XAF Fr)
* Chad (XAF Fr)
* Chile (USD $)
* China (CNY ¥)
* Christmas Island (AUD $)
* Cocos (Keeling) Islands (AUD $)
* Colombia (USD $)
* Comoros (KMF Fr)
* Congo - Brazzaville (XAF Fr)
* Congo - Kinshasa (CDF Fr)
* Cook Islands (NZD $)
* Costa Rica (CRC ₡)
* Côte d’Ivoire (XOF Fr)
* Croatia (EUR €)
* Curaçao (ANG ƒ)
* Cyprus (EUR €)
* Czechia (CZK Kč)
* Denmark (DKK kr.)
* Djibouti (DJF Fdj)
* Dominica (XCD $)
* Dominican Republic (DOP $)
* Ecuador (USD $)
* Egypt (EGP ج.م)
* El Salvador (USD $)
* Equatorial Guinea (XAF Fr)
* Eritrea (USD $)
* Estonia (EUR €)
* Eswatini (USD $)
* Ethiopia (ETB Br)
* Falkland Islands (FKP £)
* Faroe Islands (DKK kr.)
* Fiji (FJD $)
* Finland (EUR €)
* France (EUR €)
* French Guiana (EUR €)
* French Polynesia (XPF Fr)
* French Southern Territories (EUR €)
* Gabon (XOF Fr)
* Gambia (GMD D)
* Georgia (USD $)
* Germany (EUR €)
* Ghana (USD $)
* Gibraltar (GBP £)
* Greece (EUR €)
* Greenland (DKK kr.)
* Grenada (XCD $)
* Guadeloupe (EUR €)
* Guatemala (GTQ Q)
* Guernsey (GBP £)
* Guinea (GNF Fr)
* Guinea-Bissau (XOF Fr)
* Guyana (GYD $)
* Haiti (USD $)
* Honduras (HNL L)
* Hong Kong SAR (HKD $)
* Hungary (HUF Ft)
* Iceland (ISK kr)
* India (INR ₹)
* Indonesia (IDR Rp)
* Iraq (USD $)
* Ireland (EUR €)
* Isle of Man (GBP £)
* Israel (ILS ₪)
* Italy (EUR €)
* Jamaica (JMD $)
* Japan (JPY ¥)
* Jersey (USD $)
* Jordan (USD $)
* Kazakhstan (KZT 〒)
* Kenya (KES KSh)
* Kiribati (USD $)
* Kosovo (EUR €)
* Kuwait (USD $)
* Kyrgyzstan (KGS som)
* Laos (LAK ₭)
* Latvia (EUR €)
* Lebanon (LBP ل.ل)
* Lesotho (USD $)
* Liberia (USD $)
* Libya (USD $)
* Liechtenstein (CHF CHF)
* Lithuania (EUR €)
* Luxembourg (EUR €)
* Macao SAR (MOP P)
* Madagascar (USD $)
* Malawi (MWK MK)
* Malaysia (MYR RM)
* Maldives (MVR MVR)
* Mali (XOF Fr)
* Malta (EUR €)
* Martinique (EUR €)
* Mauritania (USD $)
* Mauritius (MUR ₨)
* Mayotte (EUR €)
* Mexico (USD $)
* Moldova (MDL L)
* Monaco (EUR €)
* Mongolia (MNT ₮)
* Montenegro (EUR €)
* Montserrat (XCD $)
* Morocco (MAD د.م.)
* Mozambique (USD $)
* Myanmar (Burma) (MMK K)
* Namibia (USD $)
* Nauru (AUD $)
* Nepal (NPR ₨)
* Netherlands (EUR €)
* New Caledonia (XPF Fr)
* New Zealand (NZD $)
* Nicaragua (NIO C$)
* Niger (XOF Fr)
* Nigeria (NGN ₦)
* Niue (NZD $)
* Norfolk Island (AUD $)
* North Macedonia (MKD ден)
* Norway (USD $)
* Oman (USD $)
* Pakistan (PKR ₨)
* Palestinian Territories (ILS ₪)
* Panama (USD $)
* Papua New Guinea (PGK K)
* Paraguay (PYG ₲)
* Peru (PEN S/.)
* Philippines (PHP ₱)
* Pitcairn Islands (NZD $)
* Poland (PLN zł)
* Portugal (EUR €)
* Qatar (QAR ر.ق)
* Réunion (EUR €)
* Romania (RON Lei)
* Russia (USD $)
* Rwanda (RWF FRw)
* Samoa (WST T)
* San Marino (EUR €)
* São Tomé & Príncipe (STD Db)
* Saudi Arabia (SAR ر.س)
* Senegal (XOF Fr)
* Serbia (RSD РСД)
* Seychelles (USD $)
* Sierra Leone (SLL Le)
* Singapore (SGD $)
* Sint Maarten (ANG ƒ)
* Slovakia (EUR €)
* Slovenia (EUR €)
* Solomon Islands (SBD $)
* Somalia (USD $)
* South Africa (USD $)
* South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (GBP £)
* South Korea (KRW ₩)
* South Sudan (USD $)
* Spain (EUR €)
* Sri Lanka (LKR ₨)
* St. Barthélemy (EUR €)
* St. Helena (SHP £)
* St. Kitts & Nevis (XCD $)
* St. Lucia (XCD $)
* St. Martin (EUR €)
* St. Pierre & Miquelon (EUR €)
* St. Vincent & Grenadines (XCD $)
* Sudan (USD $)
* Suriname (USD $)
* Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $)
* Sweden (SEK kr)
* Switzerland (CHF CHF)
* Taiwan (TWD $)
* Tajikistan (TJS ЅМ)
* Tanzania (TZS Sh)
* Thailand (THB ฿)
* Timor-Leste (USD $)
* Togo (XOF Fr)
* Tokelau (NZD $)
* Tonga (TOP T$)
* Trinidad & Tobago (TTD $)
* Tristan da Cunha (GBP £)
* Tunisia (USD $)
* Türkiye (USD $)
* Turkmenistan (USD $)
* Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $)
* Tuvalu (AUD $)
* U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $)
* Uganda (UGX USh)
* Ukraine (UAH ₴)
* United Arab Emirates (AED د.إ)
* United Kingdom (GBP £)
* United States (USD $)
* Uruguay (UYU $)
* Uzbekistan (UZS )
* Vanuatu (VUV Vt)
* Vatican City (EUR €)
* Venezuela (USD $)
* Vietnam (VND ₫)
* Wallis & Futuna (XPF Fr)
* Western Sahara (MAD د.م.)
* Yemen (YER ﷼)
* Zambia (USD $)
* Zimbabwe (USD $)

Update country/region

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Information** 

This Privacy Information is given by Dante Labs Inc. and Dante Labs SRL (together with Dante Labs SRL, “Dante Labs”, “We”, “Us”), with the intent to explain to you which are the purposes and means of processing your personal data. Dante Labs Inc has appointed Dante Labs SRL, with registered office at Strada Statale 17, 67100, L'Aquila (AQ), Italy, in the capacity of Data Controller, pursuant to Article 13 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (hereinafter “Regulation”).

**We do not sell your Personal Information or Genomic Data.**

**Personal Data Categories**

Dante Labs will process some of your personal information, including – but not limited to – your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number and payment and invoicing information. 

You are required to fill in with your personal data the fields flagged as obligatory in order to enable the performance of the contract, otherwise Dante Labs will not be able to accept and process your order.

Whenever you send us a biological sample after the purchase of the appropriate test, the analysis of such sample will be carried out by Dante Labs, that will process your personal data accordingly with this specific Privacy Information.

**Purposes and lawful basis for processing personal data**

We will process your personal data in order to enable you to activate and access a customer account in the website www.Dantelabs.com (hereinafter the “Website”) and/or to purchase our services through our Website. Personal data are processed, thus, to adequately perform the contract, pursuant Art. 6 (1)(b) from the Regulation, as well in order to comply with tax and accounting obligations, pursuant Art. 6(1)(c) of the Regulation.

Based on your consent, Dante Labs can, furthermore, process your e-mail address to send you newsletters and marketing communications. You are entitle to withdraw your consent by anytime writing to [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com).

**Means of data processing** 

Your personal data shall be processed both by manual and electronic means, subjected to the Regulation provisions or other applicable national laws, which includes any provisions from the competent Supervisory Authority for the protection of personal data. 

**Duration of processing activities and data retention period**

Your personal data will be processed for the strictly necessary time for the provision of the requested services; whenever you activate a personal account on the Website, your personal data will be processed until you terminate that account. Your data will be yet retained for the following 10 years solely to comply with legal obligations and to eventually safeguard Dante Labs rights.

**Third parties categories**

Dante Labs can rely on third parties for some types of data processing. In that case, these parties will be nominated Data Processors, pursuant to Art. 28 of the Regulation, and will receive the proper operative instructions, especially regarding the adoption of appropriate security measures, to guarantee data security and data confidentiality. Data subjects may require to Dante Labs a list of Data Processors writing to [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com).

**Data transfer to countries outside the European Economic Area**

Dante Labs suppliers, responsible for the execution of activities related to the services you requested, may transfer your personal data to countries located outside the European Economic Area. The data transfer is regulated by standard contractual clauses adopted by the European Commission or with due regard for any other warranties provided for by the Regulation. 

**Data subjects rights**

We inform you that, as data subject, you are entitled to exercise the rights under Articles 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23 of the Regulation writing to our e-mail address dpo@dantelabs.com.

Among other things, you may:

* ask and obtain information about whether or not Dante Labs is holding any of your personal data or whether or not your personal data are being processed and, in this case, you may have access to them; 
* ask and obtain a copy of your personal data that are processed by automated means in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format; you can also claim the right to transmit those data to another controller;
* ask and obtain the alteration and/or rectification of your personal data when you consider them to be inaccurate or incomplete;
* ask and obtain the erasure – and/or a processing restriction – of your personal data whenever they are not necessary – or no longer necessary – to fulfil the purposes for which they were collected, hence upon expiry of the retention period.

Please note that you can lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority whenever your personal data are unlawfully processed. 

Please be advised that Dante Labs Inc. has designated Dante Labs S.r.l., with registered office in Via San Giuseppe 53, 67017, Pizzoli (AQ) as its representative inside the European Union, pursuant to Art. 27 of the Regulation.

CONSENT

* I hereby give my consent for the processing of my personal data, such as my e-mail address, to newsletter distribution and marketing communication purposes. 

_Dear Customer,_

_this Privacy Information regards the performance of the analysis of the biological sample you will send to Dante Labs after buying your genetic test from Dante Labs._

_Dante Labs will be in charge to carry on with the analysis of your biological sample under your request. You may proceed with your biological sample analysis request after reading this privacy information by registering at Dante Labs website’s customer area in www.dantelabs.com._

**Privacy Information for the processing of genetic data**

This Privacy Information is given by Dante Labs Inc. and Dante Labs SRL (together with Dante Labs SRL, “Dante Labs”, “We”, “Us”), with the intent to explain to you which are the purposes and means of processing your personal data. Dante Labs Inc has appointed Dante Labs SRL, with registered office at Strada Statale 17, 67100, L'Aquila (AQ), Italy, in the capacity of Data Controller, pursuant to Article 13 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (hereinafter “Regulation”).

**Personal data categories** 

Dante Labs may process the following categories of personal data:

1. registration information, such as first and last name and contact details (registered e-mail address) to enable Dante Labs to communicate with you (e.g. to inform you when the test results are available);
2. genetic data, which means data relating to inherited or acquired genetic characteristics which give unique information about your physiology or health and which result, in particular, from the analysis of the biological sample, whenever you require for the examination of a biological sample after buying the test;

Conferring us the aforementioned data is necessary to enable Dante Labs to perform the services you required; in case of absence, Dante Labs cannot be able to perform the services you required.

**Purposes and lawful basis for processing personal data**

Personal data referred to in letter A) shall be processed in order to perform the services you required, pursuant art. 6 (1) (b) of the Regulation and in order to comply with tax and accounting obligations, pursuant Art. 6 (1) (c) of the Regulation.

Personal data referred to in letter B) shall be processed pursuant art. 9 (2) (a) of the Regulation in order to pursuit the following purposes:

1. carry out, upon your explicit consent, the genetic test you required;
2. scientific research, upon your explicit and voluntary consent.

Please note that the absence of the consent for processing your personal data for the purposes referred to in point i), means that Dante Labs will not be able to perform the services you required.

The consent for the purposes of scientific research referred to in point ii), where applicable, can be withdrawn at any time. If you want to withdraw your consent to scientific research, you can write to [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com).

**Means of data processing** 

Your personal data shall be processed both by manual and electronic means, subjected to the Regulation provisions and from the Italian national law, which includes any provisions from the Italian Supervisory Authority for the protection of personal data. 

**Duration of processing activities and data retention period** 

The test, containing the genetic sample your sent us, will be destroyed right after the results are ready and available at your account on Dante Labs website (hereinafter “Customer Area”).

Your personal data referred to in letter A) shall be processed for the period required to perform the services you requested and will be retained for the following 10 years solely to comply with legal obligations and to eventually safeguard Dante Labs rights.

Your personal data referred to in letter B) shall be processed for the period required to perform the services you requested. 

Until when you decide to deactivate your account on Dante Labs website, the report with the results will be kept available in your Customer Area to allow you to buy additional genome analysis. After the account deactivation, your personal data will be retained for the following 10 years solely to comply with legal obligations and to eventually safeguard Dante Labs rights. 

Furthermore, whenever you give us your consent to use your data for scientific research purposes, Dante Labs will process your personal data for as long as they are relevant to the research activities, until your consent is withdrawn.

**Third parties categories**

Dante Labs can rely on third parties for some types of data processing. In that case, these parties will be nominated Data Processors, pursuant to Art. 28 of the Regulation, and will receive the proper operative instructions, especially regarding the adoption of appropriate security measures, to guarantee data security and data confidentiality. Data subjects may require to Dante Labs a list of Data Processors writing to [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com).

**Data transfer to countries outside the European Economic Area** 

Dante Labs suppliers, responsible for the execution of activities related to the services you requested, may transfer your personal data to countries located outside the European Economic Area. The data transfer is regulated by standard contractual clauses adopted by the European Commission or with due regard for any other warranties provided by the Regulation.

**Data subjects rights**

We inform you that, as data subject, you are entitled to exercise the rights under Articles 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23 of the Regulation writing to our e-mail address [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com). 

Among other things, you may:

* ask and obtain information about whether or not Dante Labs is holding any of your personal data or whether or not your personal data are being processed and, in this case, you may have access to them; 
* ask and obtain a copy of your personal data that are processed by automated means in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format; you can also claim the right to transmit those data to another controller;
* ask and obtain the alteration and/or rectification of your personal data when you consider them to be inaccurate or incomplete;
* ask and obtain the erasure – and/or a processing restriction – of your personal data whenever they are not necessary – or no longer necessary – to fulfil the purposes for which they were collected, hence upon expiry of the retention period.

Please note that you can lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority whenever your personal data are unlawfully processed. 

Please be advised that Dante Labs has nominated a Data Protection Officer (DPO) that you may reach at the following address [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com). 

CONSENT

* I hereby give my consent to the processing of my genetic data for the purposes related to the analysis of my biological sample or any other service I may acquire from Dante Labs as provided in this Privacy Information.

* I hereby give my consent to the processing of my genetic data, which result from the analysis of my biological sample, for the purposes related to scientific research as provided in this Privacy Information.

**Privacy Notice for California Residents**

**Summary**

This Privacy Notice for California Residents contains information required by the California Privacy Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), as amended or replaced from time to time, along with any implementing regulations, and supplements our Main Privacy Policy. Dante Labs privacy principles are the same for all customers. For example, all customers can request a copy of their data, request deletion, and control their privacy settings in their Account Settings. This notice makes sure we cover California-specific requirements. In the event of any conflict between the terms of this notice and the Privacy Statement, the terms of this notice prevail.

Here is a summary before we dive into the details:

* You have the right to know whether we sell your Personal Information and opt-out of a sale if we do. **We do not sell your Personal Information or Genomic Data.**
* You have the right to receive an overview of the Personal Information we collect, how we use it, and who we share it with.
* You can request access to your Personal Information, get a copy, and delete your Personal Information.
* You or your authorized agent can always contact us if you have a question at dpo@dantelabs.com

**Your Rights**

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this notice, we mean any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with you, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you, and as otherwise defined in the CCPA. The CCPA does not consider publicly available information as “Personal Information.”

Let’s start with your rights first. You have the right to:

* Know what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, or sell.
* Receive a copy of your Personal Information.
* Delete your Personal Information.
* Not receive discriminatory treatment if you exercise your CCPA rights.

We make it easy to exercise your CCPA rights by making them available through your Account Settings. To access Account Settings, you must log in to your Dante Labs account.

If you do not have a Dante Labs account and would like to make a CCPA rights request, you can email us at [dpo@dantelabs.com](mailto:dpo@dantelabs.com) with the subject line “CCPA Rights Request”. We will require some additional information to verify your identity in order to process your request. Alternatively, you may exercise your CCPA rights through an authorized agent. If you use an authorized agent, we will require you to verify your identity and confirm that you have provided the authorized agent permission to submit the request on your behalf. We will respond to your request within 45 days, and in more difficult cases we may extend our response time by another 45 days. The easiest way to exercise your rights is through your Account Settings so we can quickly verify your identity. Your rights under the CCPA are not absolute and Dante Labs may exercise limitations or exemptions as permitted by the CCPA.

Dante Labs does not sell Personal Information to third parties. The CCPA provides you with the right to know whether your Personal Information is being sold and to opt-out of such sales.

**What We Collect**

As detailed in our Privacy Statement, we collect Personal Information for various purposes with privacy principles in mind. Choice and transparency are just as important to us as they are to you. The categories of Personal Information and other terms used below are defined in California Civil Code 1798.140, and may include reference to certain key definitions set forth in our Privacy Statement. Some of the categories below require separate opt-in consent and these categories do not necessarily reflect all of the types of information that we may collect about you. We will provide you a separate notice if we collect any additional Personal Information from you!

In the last twelve (12) months, we have collected the following categories of Personal Information from our customers:

* **Identifiers:**Registration Information, Web-Behavior Information, and/or User Content such as your name, display name, address, online identifier, IP address, email address, username, or other similar identifiers. We mainly use these to offer our Services, such as when you create an account with us, purchase our Services, or when you choose to connect with other customers of Dante Labs.
* **Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records provisions:**Registration Information, Self-Reported Information, and/or User Content such as your name, address, phone number, Self-Reported Information (such as details about your employment or education), and payment information (last 4 digits only). Some Personal Information included in this category may overlap with other categories. Similarly to the category above, we mainly use this information to offer our Services to you.
* **Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law:**Registration Information, Self-Reported Information, and/or User Content such as your age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, and genetic information (including familial genetic information). You can review protected classes under California law [here](https://www.senate.ca.gov/content/protected-classes). Generally this information is collected because you provide it directly to us. Certain elements, including Genetic Information, ancestry, and sex, may be developed or analyzed by Dante Labs in relation to our genetic testing services.
* **Commercial information:**Self-Reported Information and/or User Content such as products or Services purchased, obtained, or considered, survey responses regarding past purchasing history, information you share on Dante Labs forums about products you purchased or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. For example, we may keep this information when you purchase products through Dante Labs.
* **Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information:**Self-Reported Information and/or User Content you provide to us through surveys or other engagement on our platform, such as when you upload a profile picture. Generally, this information is collected directly from you, or passively collected about you with your permission.
* **Professional or employment-related information:**Self-Reported Information and/or User Content such as education, household income, occupation, and other professional information. This information can be collected when you apply for a job with Dante Labs, fill out a survey, or otherwise engage with us.
* **Biometric information:**Self-Reported Information and/or User Content such as physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics that can be used to establish an individual’s identity. To the extent we collect this information, we collect it directly from you when you choose to share it with us.
* **Internet or other electronic network activity information:**Web-Behavior Information such as data generated from your use of our Services and collected through log files, cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. Such information may include your browser type, domains, page views, how long you spent on a page or feature of the website, or other data about your engagement with our Services.
* **Geolocation data:**Web-Behavior Information that includes the identification or estimation of physical location or movement. You can learn more about how Dante Labs processes Web-Behavior Information in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.23andme.com/about/cookies/).
* **Inferences drawn from other personal information:**Inferences and Derived Data includes any information, data, assumptions, or conclusions Dante Labs infers based on analyses of facts, evidence, or another source of information or data. Dante Labs may derive Genetic Information, such as imputed genotype data, genetic risk scores, and phenotypes (which are observable characteristics or traits). Generally this information is created by Dante Labs and not collected directly from you. Dante Labs may derive information from data that was collected in relation to our genetic testing services, directly from you, or through tracking technology.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

Dante Labs may share Personal Information listed above for operational business purposes or at your direction. Such business purposes include:

* **Providing Services:**To provide our Services to you, including maintaining or servicing your account, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, and more.
* **Audit:**Auditing related to a current interaction and concurrent transactions.
* **Security:**Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity. Please see Section 4.e. of our Privacy Statement for more information.
* **Debugging:**Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
* **Transient Use:**Short-term, transient use, where personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction.
* **Dante Labs Product Research and Development:**Research that Dante Labs performs to improve and develop its products and services.
* **Quality Assurance and Product Improvement:**Activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by Dante Labs, and otherwise to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by Dante Labs.

If you have given your explicit consent, for example via a data transfer authorization or other consent document, we may share your Personal Information for commercial purposes. The purpose, such as recruitment for external research, may vary and will be described in the consent.

**Changes to this notice**

Dante Labs will periodically review and update this notice. We recommend visiting this page to stay aware of any changes. If we modify this notice, we will make the revised notice available through our website.

Company

Legal Info

Contacts

Subscribe to our newsletter

Unlock special offers and receive timely updates from our knowledgeable experts.

 Email

 I agree to receiving marketing emails and special deals

* * *

 English

* English  United Kingdom (GBP £)

* Afghanistan (AFN ؋)
* Åland Islands (EUR €)
* Albania (ALL L)
* Algeria (DZD د.ج)
* Andorra (EUR €)
* Angola (USD $)
* Anguilla (XCD $)
* Antigua & Barbuda (XCD $)
* Argentina (USD $)
* Armenia (AMD դր.)
* Aruba (AWG ƒ)
* Ascension Island (SHP £)
* Australia (AUD $)
* Austria (EUR €)
* Azerbaijan (AZN ₼)
* Bahamas (BSD $)
* Bahrain (USD $)
* Bangladesh (BDT ৳)
* Barbados (BBD $)
* Belarus (USD $)
* Belgium (EUR €)
* Belize (BZD $)
* Benin (XOF Fr)
* Bermuda (USD $)
* Bhutan (USD $)
* Bolivia (BOB Bs.)
* Bosnia & Herzegovina (BAM КМ)
* Botswana (BWP P)
* Brazil (USD $)
* British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $)
* British Virgin Islands (USD $)
* Brunei (BND $)
* Bulgaria (BGN лв.)
* Burkina Faso (XOF Fr)
* Burundi (BIF Fr)
* Cambodia (KHR ៛)
* Cameroon (XAF Fr)
* Canada (CAD $)
* Cape Verde (CVE $)
* Caribbean Netherlands (USD $)
* Cayman Islands (KYD $)
* Central African Republic (XAF Fr)
* Chad (XAF Fr)
* Chile (USD $)
* China (CNY ¥)
* Christmas Island (AUD $)
* Cocos (Keeling) Islands (AUD $)
* Colombia (USD $)
* Comoros (KMF Fr)
* Congo - Brazzaville (XAF Fr)
* Congo - Kinshasa (CDF Fr)
* Cook Islands (NZD $)
* Costa Rica (CRC ₡)
* Côte d’Ivoire (XOF Fr)
* Croatia (EUR €)
* Curaçao (ANG ƒ)
* Cyprus (EUR €)
* Czechia (CZK Kč)
* Denmark (DKK kr.)
* Djibouti (DJF Fdj)
* Dominica (XCD $)
* Dominican Republic (DOP $)
* Ecuador (USD $)
* Egypt (EGP ج.م)
* El Salvador (USD $)
* Equatorial Guinea (XAF Fr)
* Eritrea (USD $)
* Estonia (EUR €)
* Eswatini (USD $)
* Ethiopia (ETB Br)
* Falkland Islands (FKP £)
* Faroe Islands (DKK kr.)
* Fiji (FJD $)
* Finland (EUR €)
* France (EUR €)
* French Guiana (EUR €)
* French Polynesia (XPF Fr)
* French Southern Territories (EUR €)
* Gabon (XOF Fr)
* Gambia (GMD D)
* Georgia (USD $)
* Germany (EUR €)
* Ghana (USD $)
* Gibraltar (GBP £)
* Greece (EUR €)
* Greenland (DKK kr.)
* Grenada (XCD $)
* Guadeloupe (EUR €)
* Guatemala (GTQ Q)
* Guernsey (GBP £)
* Guinea (GNF Fr)
* Guinea-Bissau (XOF Fr)
* Guyana (GYD $)
* Haiti (USD $)
* Honduras (HNL L)
* Hong Kong SAR (HKD $)
* Hungary (HUF Ft)
* Iceland (ISK kr)
* India (INR ₹)
* Indonesia (IDR Rp)
* Iraq (USD $)
* Ireland (EUR €)
* Isle of Man (GBP £)
* Israel (ILS ₪)
* Italy (EUR €)
* Jamaica (JMD $)
* Japan (JPY ¥)
* Jersey (USD $)
* Jordan (USD $)
* Kazakhstan (KZT 〒)
* Kenya (KES KSh)
* Kiribati (USD $)
* Kosovo (EUR €)
* Kuwait (USD $)
* Kyrgyzstan (KGS som)
* Laos (LAK ₭)
* Latvia (EUR €)
* Lebanon (LBP ل.ل)
* Lesotho (USD $)
* Liberia (USD $)
* Libya (USD $)
* Liechtenstein (CHF CHF)
* Lithuania (EUR €)
* Luxembourg (EUR €)
* Macao SAR (MOP P)
* Madagascar (USD $)
* Malawi (MWK MK)
* Malaysia (MYR RM)
* Maldives (MVR MVR)
* Mali (XOF Fr)
* Malta (EUR €)
* Martinique (EUR €)
* Mauritania (USD $)
* Mauritius (MUR ₨)
* Mayotte (EUR €)
* Mexico (USD $)
* Moldova (MDL L)
* Monaco (EUR €)
* Mongolia (MNT ₮)
* Montenegro (EUR €)
* Montserrat (XCD $)
* Morocco (MAD د.م.)
* Mozambique (USD $)
* Myanmar (Burma) (MMK K)
* Namibia (USD $)
* Nauru (AUD $)
* Nepal (NPR ₨)
* Netherlands (EUR €)
* New Caledonia (XPF Fr)
* New Zealand (NZD $)
* Nicaragua (NIO C$)
* Niger (XOF Fr)
* Nigeria (NGN ₦)
* Niue (NZD $)
* Norfolk Island (AUD $)
* North Macedonia (MKD ден)
* Norway (USD $)
* Oman (USD $)
* Pakistan (PKR ₨)
* Palestinian Territories (ILS ₪)
* Panama (USD $)
* Papua New Guinea (PGK K)
* Paraguay (PYG ₲)
* Peru (PEN S/.)
* Philippines (PHP ₱)
* Pitcairn Islands (NZD $)
* Poland (PLN zł)
* Portugal (EUR €)
* Qatar (QAR ر.ق)
* Réunion (EUR €)
* Romania (RON Lei)
* Russia (USD $)
* Rwanda (RWF FRw)
* Samoa (WST T)
* San Marino (EUR €)
* São Tomé & Príncipe (STD Db)
* Saudi Arabia (SAR ر.س)
* Senegal (XOF Fr)
* Serbia (RSD РСД)
* Seychelles (USD $)
* Sierra Leone (SLL Le)
* Singapore (SGD $)
* Sint Maarten (ANG ƒ)
* Slovakia (EUR €)
* Slovenia (EUR €)
* Solomon Islands (SBD $)
* Somalia (USD $)
* South Africa (USD $)
* South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (GBP £)
* South Korea (KRW ₩)
* South Sudan (USD $)
* Spain (EUR €)
* Sri Lanka (LKR ₨)
* St. Barthélemy (EUR €)
* St. Helena (SHP £)
* St. Kitts & Nevis (XCD $)
* St. Lucia (XCD $)
* St. Martin (EUR €)
* St. Pierre & Miquelon (EUR €)
* St. Vincent & Grenadines (XCD $)
* Sudan (USD $)
* Suriname (USD $)
* Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $)
* Sweden (SEK kr)
* Switzerland (CHF CHF)
* Taiwan (TWD $)
* Tajikistan (TJS ЅМ)
* Tanzania (TZS Sh)
* Thailand (THB ฿)
* Timor-Leste (USD $)
* Togo (XOF Fr)
* Tokelau (NZD $)
* Tonga (TOP T$)
* Trinidad & Tobago (TTD $)
* Tristan da Cunha (GBP £)
* Tunisia (USD $)
* Türkiye (USD $)
* Turkmenistan (USD $)
* Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $)
* Tuvalu (AUD $)
* U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $)
* Uganda (UGX USh)
* Ukraine (UAH ₴)
* United Arab Emirates (AED د.إ)
* United Kingdom (GBP £)
* United States (USD $)
* Uruguay (UYU $)
* Uzbekistan (UZS )
* Vanuatu (VUV Vt)
* Vatican City (EUR €)
* Venezuela (USD $)
* Vietnam (VND ₫)
* Wallis & Futuna (XPF Fr)
* Western Sahara (MAD د.م.)
* Yemen (YER ﷼)
* Zambia (USD $)
* Zimbabwe (USD $)

Update country/region

Amazon

American Express

Apple Pay

Diners Club

Discover

Meta Pay

Google Pay

Mastercard

Shop Pay

Visa

© 2024 Dante Labs US, 12 East 49th Street, 18th Floor New York, NY 10017[](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

Cart 0

Your cart is currently empty.

Search 

Trending Now

* [

    Quick view](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/achromatopsia-panel "Achromatopsia Report")
    
    [Achromatopsia Report](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/achromatopsia-panel "Achromatopsia Report") £24.00 /
    
* [

    Quick view](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/acmg-panel "ACMG Report")
    
    [ACMG Report](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/acmg-panel "ACMG Report") £24.00 /
    
* [

    Quick view](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/acrodermatitis-enteropathica-panel "Acrodermatitis Enteropathica Report")
    
    [Acrodermatitis Enteropathica Report](https://us.dantelabs.com/products/acrodermatitis-enteropathica-panel "Acrodermatitis Enteropathica Report") £24.00 /
